A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Division Files, 2
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 205)
  - Division Monthly Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Fellowships - Data Lists and Memoranda, 1927-1950 (Box 15, Folder 207)
  - Fellowships - Dieticians (A-W), 1933-1941 (Box 15, Folder 208)
  - Fellowships - Nurses (C-W), 1929-1947 (Box 15, Folder 209)
  - Fellowships - Nurses (Course Syllabus), 1939 (Box 15, Folder 210)
  - Fellowships - Nurses (Memoranda), 1928-1929 (Box 15, Folder 211)
  - Fellowships - Physicians (Harvard), 1926-1947 (Box 15, Folder 212)
  - Fellowships - Physicians (Kansas), 1928-1935 (Box 15, Folder 213)
  - Fellowships - Physicians (Ma-Mu), 1937-1947 (Box 15, Folder 214)
  - Fellowships - Physicians (Re-Tufts), 1928-1948 (Box 15, Folder 215)
  - Fellowships - Tulane, 1928-1930 (Box 15, Folder 216)
  - Fellowships - Tulane, 1932-1947 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Fellowships (Utah-Yale), 1928-1938 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - Hospital Appraisals - Beloit, Kansas, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - Hospital Appraisals - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee; Farmington, Maine, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 220)
  - Hospital Appraisals - Farmville, Virginia; Glasgow, Kentucky, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 221)
  - Hospital Appraisals - Kingsport, Tennessee; Murfreesboro, Tennessee, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 222)
  - Hospital Appraisals - Tupelo, Mississippi; Wauseon, Ohio, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 223)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 224)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 225)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 226)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 227)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 228)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 229)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1943-1946 (Box 16, Folder 230)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1947 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Grant File, 1943-1945 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Grant File, 1943-1945 (Box 17, Folder 233)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Grant File, 1943-1945 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Grant File, 1943-1945 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - Hospital Survey/Commission on Hospital Care (COHC) - Minutes, 1944-1946 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 237)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 239)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 240)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 241)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 242)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 243)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 244)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1925-1932 (Box 17, Folder 245)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 246)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 247)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 248)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 249)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 250)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 251)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 254)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 255)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 256)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1932-1945 (Box 18, Folder 257)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1946-1951 (Box 19, Folder 258)
  - Interoffice Memos, 1946-1951 (Box 19, Folder 259)
  - Medical Education Program - Correspondence (A-Y), 1928-1943 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - Medical Education Program - Memoranda, 1927-1944 (Box 19, Folder 261)
  - Medical Education Program - Memoranda, 1927-1944 (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - Medical Education Program - Memoranda, 1927-1944 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Medical Education Program - Memoranda, 1927-1944 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - News Releases (Farmville, Virginia), February 6, 1926 (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - News Releases (Farmville, Virginia), September 20, 1926 (Box 19, Folder 266)
  - News Releases (Beloit, Kansas; Wauseon, Ohio), October 24, 1927 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Nursing Appraisals, 1936-1945 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Out-Patient Department - Reports and Memoranda, 1928-1944 (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Out-Patient Department - Reports and Memoranda, 1928-1944 (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Preliminary Correspondence, 1924-1926 (Box 20, Folder 271)
  - Printed Material (Appeal Forms), 1926-1944 (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - Printed Material (Appeal Forms), 1926-1944 (Box 20, Folder 273)
  - Program Expansion Memoranda, 1931-1933 (Box 20, Folder 274)
  - Publications - Reprint of Annual Report (Correspondence and Memoranda), 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Publications - Small Community Hospitals (Correspondence and Memoranda), 1943-1946 (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Publications - Small Hospital Design (Correspondence and Memoranda), 1931-1937 (Box 20, Folder 277)
  - Publicity, 1925-1931 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Ada, Oklahoma; Beloit, Kansas; Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Farmington, Maine; Farmville, Virginia), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Glasgow, Kentucky; Kingsport, Tennessee), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Lancaster, South Carolina), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Mt. Pleasant, Michigan; Murfreesboro, Tennessee), n.d. (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Pittsfield, Illinois; Provo, Utah), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 284)
  - Rates of Charges - Hospitals (Sikeston, Missouri; Tupelo, Mississippi; Wauseon, Ohio), n.d. (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Rates of Charges - Services, 1931-1938; 1941-1948 (Box 21, Folder 286)
  - Rates of Charges - Services, 1931-1938; 1941-1948 (Box 21, Folder 287)
  - Regional Plan - Agreements (Correspondence and Drafts), April-September, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 288)
  - Regional Plan - Agreements (Correspondence and Drafts-Federal Aid), 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 289)
  - Regional Plan - Agreements (Correspondence and Drafts-Federal Aid), 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 290)
  - Regional Plan - Announcements, April 1944 (Box 21, Folder 291)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Atlanta, Georgia), July-November, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 292)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Atlanta, Georgia), July-November, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 293)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Atlanta, Georgia), July-November, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 294)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Miscellaneous Sites-Alabama-Pennsylvania), 1943-1945 (Box 21, Folder 295)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Miscellaneous Sites-Tennessee to Vermont), 1943-1945 (Box 21, Folder 296)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Richmond, Virginia), 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 297)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Richmond, Virginia), 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 298)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Richmond, Virginia), 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 299)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Richmond, Virginia), 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 300)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Richmond, Virginia), 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 301)
  - Regional Plan - Appeals (Richmond, Virginia), 1944-1947 (Box 22, Folder 302)
  - Regional Plan - Budget Outline, April 1945 (Box 22, Folder 303)
  - Regional Plan - Constitution and By-Laws (Rochester, New York), November 1945 (Box 22, Folder 304)
  - Regional Plan - Correspondence, 1946-1951 (Box 22, Folder 305)
  - Regional Plan - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 306)
  - Regional Plan - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 307)
  - Regional Plan - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1945 (Box 22, Folder 308)
  - Regional Plan - Name Folder (A-F), 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 309)
  - Regional Plan - Name Folder (H-N), 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - Regional Plan - Name Folder (O-W), 1943-1944 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Regional Plan - Site Selection Reports, August-October, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 312)
  - Report on the Study of 12 Small Hospitals (T. Krater and A. C. Haupt) - Preliminary Report (Box 23, Folder 313)
  - Report on the Study of 12 Small Hospitals (T. Krater and A. C. Haupt) - Report of June 5, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 314)
  - Reports/Recommendations for Rural Hospital Sites - Project #1 (Henry C. Wright Report), December 14, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 315)
  - Reports/Recommendations for Rural Hospital Sites - Projects #2-5, 1926-1930 (Box 23, Folder 316)
  - Reports/Recommendations for Rural Hospital Sites - Projects #6-9, 1933-1935 (Box 23, Folder 317)
  - Reports/Recommendations for Rural Hospital Sites - Projects #10-12, 1937-1942 (Box 23, Folder 318)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Ada, Oklahoma; Beloit, Kansas) (Box 23, Folder 319)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee; Farmington, Maine) (Box 23, Folder 320)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Farmville, Virginia) (Box 23, Folder 321)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Glasgow, Kentucky; Kingsport, Tennessee) (Box 23, Folder 322)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Lancaster, South Carolina; Mt. Pleasant, Michigan; Murfreesboro, Tennessee) (Box 23, Folder 323)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Pittsfield, Illinois; Provo, Utah; Sikeston, Missouri; Tupelo, Mississippi) (Box 23, Folder 324)
  - Rules and Regulations - Hospitals (Wauseon, Ohio) (Box 23, Folder 325)
  - Rules and Regulations - Memoranda and Drafts, 1929-1949 (Box 24, Folder 326)
  - Rules and Regulations - Memoranda and Drafts, 1929-1949 (Box 24, Folder 327)
  - Service Records Manual, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 328)
  - Service Records Manual, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 329)
  - Service Records Manual, Undated (Box 24, Folder 330)
  - Service Records Manual, Undated (Box 24, Folder 331)
  - Set-up and Organization of a Rural Hospital - Memoranda Correspondence and Reports, 1926-1935 (Box 24, Folder 332)
  - Set-up and Organization of a Rural Hospital - Southmayd Report, Undated (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Statistics - All Hospital General Statistics, 1930-1947 (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - Statistics - Annual Financial, 1932-1943 (Box 24, Folder 335)
  - Statistics - Annual Financial, 1932-1943 (Box 24, Folder 336)
  - Statistics - Annual Financial, 1932-1943 (Box 24, Folder 337)
  - Statistics - Annual Financial, 1944-1948 (Box 25, Folder 338)
  - Statistics - Annual Financial, 1944-1948 (Box 25, Folder 339)
  - Statistics - Annual Professional, 1942-1948 (Box 25, Folder 340)
  - Statistics - Annual Professional, 1942-1948 (Box 25, Folder 341)
  - Statistics - Annual Professional, 1942-1948 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - Statistics - Cost Analysis, 1930-1946 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - Statistics - Cost Analysis, 1930-1946 (Box 25, Folder 344)
  - Statistics - Program, 1925-1940 (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Statistics - Program, 1925-1940 (Box 25, Folder 346)
  - Statistics - Program, 1925-1940 (Box 25, Folder 347)
  - Statistics - Program, 1925-1940 (Box 25, Folder 348)
  - Statistics - Program, 1925-1940 (Box 25, Folder 349)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 350)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 351)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 352)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 353)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 354)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 355)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 356)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 357)
  - Statistics - Program, 1941-1948 (Box 26, Folder 358)
  - Statistics - Report Summaries, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 359)
  - Statistics - Report Summaries, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 360)
  - Statistics - Report Summaries, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 361)
  - Statistics - Report Summaries, 1928-1935 (Box 26, Folder 362)
  - Superintendent's Conference - Program Material, April-May, 1930 (Box 26, Folder 363)
- Project Files, 3
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Audit Reports, 1937-1938; 1945-1948 (Box 27, Folder 364)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Agreements, 1937-1945 (Box 27, Folder 365)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions (Box 27, Folder 366)
    Change Orders - April 14, 1937-April 28, 1938 Purchase Orders - November 29, 1937-August 10, 1939
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1937-1942 (Box 27, Folder 367)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1937-1942 (Box 27, Folder 368)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1937-1942 (Box 27, Folder 369)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1937-1942 (Box 27, Folder 370)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data Sheets, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 371)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Building Requisitions - Equipment Data Sheets, 1938 (Box 27, Folder 372)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Disbursements, 1939-1946 (Box 27, Folder 373)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 374)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 375)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 376)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 377)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1940 (Box 27, Folder 378)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Equipment - Sales Literature, 1937-1940 (Box 28, Folder 379)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Fellowships (B-G), 1938-1942 (Box 28, Folder 380)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Fellowships (L-S), 1938-1942 (Box 28, Folder 381)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1948 (Box 28, Folder 382)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1948 (Box 28, Folder 383)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1948 (Box 28, Folder 384)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1948 (Box 28, Folder 385)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Field Trip Memoranda, 1936-1948 (Box 28, Folder 386)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 387)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 388)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 389)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 390)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 391)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1935-1937 (Box 28, Folder 392)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 393)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 394)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 395)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 396)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 397)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 398)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 399)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 400)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 401)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1937-1949; 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 402)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Hospital Proper - Correspondence Index, 1935-1949 (Box 29, Folder 403)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, 1935-1948 (Box 29, Folder 404)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, 1935-1948 (Box 29, Folder 405)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, 1935-1948 (Box 29, Folder 406)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 29, Folder 407)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1936-1940 (Box 29, Folder 408)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 409)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 410)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 411)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 412)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 413)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 414)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Monthly Reports, 1941-1949 (Box 30, Folder 415)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Oklahoma State Department of Health - License Laws and Standards for Hospitals and Related Institutions, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 416)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1942 (Box 30, Folder 417)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1938-1942 (Box 30, Folder 418)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1939-1944 (Box 30, Folder 419)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Public Health Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1937-1944 (Box 30, Folder 420)
  - Ada, Oklahoma - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1938-1947 (Box 30, Folder 421)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Audit Reports, 1930, 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 422)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Audit Reports, 1930, 1947-1949 (Box 31, Folder 423)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Agreements, 1928-1930; 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 424)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Agreements, 1928-1930; 1940-1942 (Box 31, Folder 425)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1944 (Box 31, Folder 426)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1944 (Box 31, Folder 427)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1944 (Box 31, Folder 428)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1944 (Box 31, Folder 429)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1928-1944 (Box 31, Folder 430)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Disbursements, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 431)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Disbursements, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 432)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1929-1935 (Box 31, Folder 433)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1929-1935 (Box 31, Folder 434)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Equipment - Purchase Orders, 1929-1935 (Box 31, Folder 435)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Fellowships (A-F), 1929-1945 (Box 31, Folder 436)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Fellowships (H-M), 1929-1945 (Box 31, Folder 437)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Fellowships (N-S), 1929-1945 (Box 32, Folder 438)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Fellowships (V-S), 1929-1945 (Box 32, Folder 439)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 440)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 441)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 442)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 443)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 444)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 445)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 446)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Field Trip Memoranda, 1927-1947 (Box 32, Folder 447)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 32, Folder 448)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 32, Folder 449)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 32, Folder 450)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 32, Folder 451)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 32, Folder 452)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 453)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 454)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 455)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 456)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 457)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 458)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 459)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 460)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 461)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 462)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 463)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 464)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 465)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1931-1947 (Box 33, Folder 466)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 467)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 468)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence, 1948-1965 (Box 34, Folder 469)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence Index, 1926-1951 (Box 34, Folder 470)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Hospital Proper - Correspondence Index, 1926-1951 (Box 34, Folder 471)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1929-1937; June 17, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 472)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1929-1937; June 17, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 473)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Minutes - Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1929-1937; June 17, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 474)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Monthly Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 475)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 34, Folder 476)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 34, Folder 477)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 34, Folder 478)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 34, Folder 479)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 34, Folder 480)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Out-Patient Department - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1930-1947 (Box 34, Folder 481)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Prepayment Plan - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1948 (Box 34, Folder 482)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Public Health Program - Correspondence Memoranda and Reports, 1927-1932 (Box 35, Folder 483)
    Indexed.
  - Beloit, Kansas - Publicity - Memoranda and Press Releases, 1930-1951 (Box 35, Folder 484)
  - Beloit, Kansas - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1930-1947 (Box 35, Folder 485)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Audit Reports, 1940; 1943 (Box 35, Folder 486)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Bonds and Agreements, 1939-1942 (Box 35, Folder 487)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1947 (Box 35, Folder 488)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1947 (Box 35, Folder 489)
  - Bristol, Virginia/Tennessee - Building Requisitions - Correspondence and Vouchers, 1938-1947 (Box 35, Folder 490)